3cx.com 2013-11-21

# 3CX Privacy Policy

**Introduction**  
We are committed to fair information practices and we respect the privacy and security of our users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users, and we may also ask you for personal information that enables us to give you access to some parts of our web site. We will not disclose your information to any person outside our organisation except as described in this Privacy Policy.

To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing our privacy practices. This statement describes what personal identifying information is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collected By Us**  
We collect certain information from and about our visitors in three ways: from our web server logs, by means of cookies, and directly from you.

**Web Server Logs**  
When you visit our 3CX sites, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include your internet protocol address, what kind of browser or computer you use, the number of links you click within the site, the state or country from which you accessed the site, the date and time of your visit, the name of your internet services provider, the last page you viewed before visiting our site, and the pages you viewed on the site.

**Cookies**  
If your browser allows it, our web sites use cookies, which are small text files which you computer creates or modifies on instruction of the page opened in your browser. These are used to save your preferences and login information. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings.

**Information From You**  
Visitors can register to obtain access to some parts of our web site (i.e support pages). When you register, we will ask you for some personal information. Some of the information requested will be required for registration, and some may be optional. Also, we may ask you to disclose personal information to enable us to provide assistance and information to you.

**Use Of And Access To Information**

**Security and Confidentiality**  
We use technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control and information about our subscribers and their website usage is maintained in a secure environment. Information about our subscribers and their website usage is not shared with third parties for marketing purposes. We do not disclose any information about any subscribers’ usage of our website except in specific cases, and we do not share information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes unless you expressly give us permission to do so.

**Identifiable Information**  
We will share your personal data as required by law or by the order of any competent court or (semi-)governmental authority or in matters of public safety or policy. Under strict conditions of confidentiality we may share your personal data with agents and contractors who use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us. We will also share your personal data as may be needed in connection with the enforcement of agreements.

**Anonymous Information**  
We may provide summary statistics about our interests and preferences of visitors of our web site, traffic patterns and related site information. These statistics do not include personally identifiable information.

**Promotional Messages**  
You will not receive any promotional messages from us unless you opted to allow us to do so. If you don’t want to receive promotional materials from us, you can opt out at any time. Please use our contact page to send us a message clearly stating that you wish to opt out and stop receiving promotional messages.

**Privacy Policy Changes  
**If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post and highlight the policy changes.

This privacy policy has last been updated on 26 January 2011.
